{
    "subject": "resource/The_Hour_of_13",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Hour of 13 is located in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9368041157722473,
            "question": "Where is The Hour of 13 located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8349857926368713,
            "question": "What state in the United States is home to The Hour of 13?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8214829564094543,
            "question": "In which country is The Hour of 13 situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7965079545974731,
            "question": "What type of place is The Hour of 13?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6481989026069641,
            "question": "What activities might visitors find at The Hour of 13?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663776397705078,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks near The Hour of 13?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49626702070236206,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the history of The Hour of 13?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42590293288230896,
            "question": "Is The Hour of 13 a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36364150047302246,
            "question": "Could The Hour of 13 be a museum or historical landmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35884207487106323,
            "question": "Is The Hour of 13 found in Europe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Hour of 13 is located in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7481_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could The Hour of 13 be a museum or historical landmark?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7481_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Hour of 13 a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7481_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the history of The Hour of 13?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7481_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_171.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7481_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"The Hour of 13 is located in the United States\", I will search for relevant information in the context.\n\nHere are my findings:\n\n* The documents mention that \"The Hour of 13 was made at the MGM-British Studios in Borehamwood, England\".\n* There is no mention of the movie being located or filmed in the United States.\n* However, the documents do mention that a conservative talk radio host said the movie was \"an indictment\" that \u201cwill leave those who will open their eyes and ears to see and hear seething about Hillary\u2019s massive fail that night in 2012\u201d which refers to Benghazi, but this does not necessarily imply that The Hour of 13 is located or filmed in the US.\n\nGiven these findings, I conclude:\n\n{ \"output\": \"no\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information provided that suggests \"The Hour of 13\" is specifically located or set in the United States. The text mentions that the film was produced by MGM-British Studios and has a setting reminiscent of Jack-the-Ripper's old London, but there is no indication it is set or filmed in the U.S."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The film \"The Hour of 13\" is not located in the United States, as it was made at MGM-British Studios in Borehamwood, England.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information about the film's production explicitly states it was made at MGM-British Studios in Borehamwood, England.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because The Hour of 13 was made at the MGM-British Studios in Borehamwood, England.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The Hour of 13 was filmed at the MGM-British Studios in Borehamwood, England, not in the United States.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}